

# Darcy Elsing PRICE

DEVELOPER

## PROFILE

With two+ years' commercial development experience, I have worked to provide a range of solutions with a multitude of technologies.

After initially pursuing a career in corporate law, I decided to transition to a developer. Within four months, I had left my career in law and was working as a freelance developer. In addition to freelance development, in 2018, I moved to South Korea to also work as a teacher in South Korea.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

### FREELANCE DEVELOPER

Freelance | South Korea | 2017-present

Worked with a range of technologies and use whichever is best suited to each task:

- Built and launched a crypto company
- Built several Discord Bot alerts that alert finance communities on certain price trends,
- Upgraded multiple HTML websites to modern static webpages using React and Gatsby/Next.js

## **TEACHER**

Pusan National University | South Korea | 2018-present

I undertake lessons for undergraduate students and assist with research on economic, trade and legal systems in Asia.

#### JUNIOR LAWYER

ANV Syndicates Limited | London | 2015-2018

I provided legal advice and researched senior lawyers. I had a specialty focus on technology and intellectual property law.

+81 10-4797-0819



darcyeprice@hotmail.com



darcyeprice.com



darcvprice **G** 



# EDUCATION

#### JURIS DOCTOR

Law

University of Sydney 2012-2014

#### **BACHELOR OF BUSINESS**

Finance

University of Technology, Sydney 2009-2011

# SKILLS

JavaScript

React/Redux

PHP

Python

SQL & AWS

## PROJECTS

## SocialApe

social-application.netlify.com

A social media application where users can post, share, like, and comment on each others' posts.

 A full-stack application using React/Redux and NodeJS/Firebase.

## **4D Crypto Business**

4dmarkets.com && trade.4dmarkets.com && dint.info
I worked with a team to launch a crypto company, including:

- Assisting with the development of an exchange using Vue.
- Building/upgrading various websites using React,
- Linking the various aspects of the business together with APIs
- Organized a group of developers to meet various competing deadlines

## WaygookTeacher

waygookteacher.com

To connect language-learners with expert teachers, by allowing users to complete their profile, update their calendar and send messages.

- Motivated by a desire to conveniently have language-lessons with Korean teachers while living in Korea.
- Incorporated PayPal to act as a payment intermediary between student and teacher.
- Integrated payment platforms to act as a secure payment intermediary.

#### Discord Bot

A range of Discord Bots, from admin duties to price alerts. Specifically, the Bots are tailored toward the financial markets community and give price alerts when various price conditions are satisfied. Accordingly, each alert is based on a different algorithm that can be adjusted to apply to each particular financial market

• Worked with other devs to build an accurate algorithm to reflect financial trends.

#### AudioWiki

wiki-audio.netlify.com/

Listen to Wikipedia articles! If you search for any Wiki article, it will extract the text and allow you to choose the language and speed for the text to be read. Inspired by a love of audiobooks!

• The text is extracted with the MediaWiki API and spoken with the WebSpeech API.

## HIGHLIGHTS

2+ years of commercial experience in development

5+ years of commercial experience working in a corporate team environment

Highly-driven desire and ability to learn difficult things quickly.

## EXTRAS

#### freeCodeCamp Korea

2018-present

Organise weekly seminar sessions and algorithm-solving competitions.

## Mera Gao Power

2016

Provided commercial advice for the installation of off-grid solar energy in rural India.

# INTERESTS

3D Printing

Stand-up comedy

Surfing

Cycling